[Music]
Kevin place is looking
great
[Applause]
couch want to help me move the couch so
I can
vacuum ready yeah ready one two
oh oh yeah do you mind if I first
dropped on the
ground ago I had a dollar no here's the
thing I'm usually honestly the one that
has the most dollars so statistically
but I don't need it but it is probably
yeah I mean I'm I I was always kind of
more of a cash
guy
credit I have a shoe box in my room that
I just no I feel like you guys you guys
need it the most I don't need it the
most necessarily okay yeah I need it I
don't need it I don't need it I need it
yeah but I don't I think we agree that
it's not your I agree that you need it
because of how your life is going but I
earned it because of hard work and
education and I so need it I'm just
going to say I need it it's my
dollar I don't it's my
dollar you can't just say that you can't
just say no honestly I don't mean to
attack but this is typical of you but
you do attack you do attack constantly I
don't want this to compromise to come do
you remember last no cuz I don't I don't
remember Jack I don't remember what I
remember is I'm usually statistically
remember I was like we should get some
strippers and I was the strippers thing
you threw up dollars and no strippers
came hey hey look let's just just leave
the
dollar that's it's not worth it yeah I
mean he's right man it's like it's just
a dollar we're yelling at each other
just leave it for the next people to
live here it's like a good deed Good
Deed do our Good Deed leave leave my
dollar leave a dollar leave the dollar
yeah screw it let's just yeah just a
dollar bury the secret my friends a
dollar over a dollar what are we crazy
if I had a dollar for every time we
fought over a dollar I'd have a dollar
we're best friends we're best friends
we're best friends go our separate ways
and then we'll all be fine about
it hey hey you get back here I knew to
do this like
Jack all right you can have the dollar
it's Jack's dollar it's your
[Music]
dollar oh PE you the economy stink hurts
stinks with look at way down in the Dow
Jones and how inflation is affecting you
just like And subscribe what's weird
things you do with money
[Music]
money